letgetmorefollowers.info 2012-01-26

# Let Get More Twitter Followers | Get More Followers on Twitter | How to Get More Twitter Followers

##     
New, Let Get More Followers.

****

**Home | Privacy Policy | Terms Of Use | FAQ | Remove Your Account **

* * *

**Last Members Get More Twitter Followers**  
  
---  

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

**Privacy Policy**

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and explains data collection and use practices for the LETGETMOREFOLLOWERS.INFO. The "LetGetMoreFollowers Network" includes all Web pages, newsletters, discussion forums and lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by LetGetMoreFollowers or indirectly from the LETGETMOREFOLLOWERS.INFO (collectively the "Site") home page (collectively hereafter "LetGetMoreFollowers"). By accessing the LetGetMoreFollowers Network, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

We promise that we will use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy as follows:

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**

**Do You Store Twitter Account Information?  
**   
In order to provide the service we offer we need to keep your twitter login information stored in our database so that we can assist you with generating more followers. Unlike many other similar services we encrypt our data so that your privacy is protected and secured using the latest in server security. We respect your privacy and we will never disclose, sell or trade this information. We also use this to occassionaly send out promotional "Tweets" for our service or websites in our network. These are to assist you in gaining more followers and make the most out of our service.

**Do you collect IP addresses?  
**   
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the LetGetMoreFollowers Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Sites. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the LetGetMoreFollowers Network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

**What are cookies?  
**   
From time to time, LetGetMoreFollowers or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of LetGetMoreFollowers's Network you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our Site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**What personal information do you collect?  
**   
Wherever LetGetMoreFollowers collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, e-mail address, phone number, work or home address, information about your job function, information about your company, and credit card information.

We may request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a contest or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to announcement lists or information about products and services). Participation in contests or other promotions on the LetGetMoreFollowers Network is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose personal information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.

If you are purchasing something on the LetGetMoreFollowers Network, we, and any third party provider, need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address. This allows us, or third party providers, to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. Your information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose except as provided in this Privacy Policy without your express permission.

LetGetMoreFollowers also offers access to some services that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail.

We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new products and services. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive postal mailings from LetGetMoreFollowers.

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

LetGetMoreFollowers will disclose personal information and/or an IP address:

**1) When required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:  
**   
a) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on LetGetMoreFollowers;

b) Protect and defend the rights or property of the LetGetMoreFollowers Network of sites and related properties, or visitors to the LetGetMoreFollowers Network of sites and related properties;

c) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the LetGetMoreFollowers legal notice and Web site User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the LetGetMoreFollowers Network or its related properties;

d) Fulfill a user's order or request;

**2) To process and fulfill your order or notify you of order status;  
**   
**3) When we have your consent to share the information;  
**   
We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

What else should I know about my privacy when online?

LetGetMoreFollowers may use third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you based on information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our web site in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites.

The LetGetMoreFollowers Network may contain hyperlinks to third party Web sites. The LetGetMoreFollowers Network may also contain advertisements of third parties. LetGetMoreFollowers is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers. LetGetMoreFollowers does not share any of the individual personal information you provide LetGetMoreFollowers with the third parties to which LetGetMoreFollowers links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although LetGetMoreFollowers may share general, aggregate data with such third parties (such as how many people use our Site). Please check with those Web sites to determine their privacy policy.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Certain LetGetMoreFollowers media properties use a shopping cart feature that safeguards this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. Other LetGetMoreFollowers media properties do not use SSL and thereby do not offer a secure coded way to transfer information.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Your Consent To This Agreement  
**   
By using the LetGetMoreFollowers Network, you consent to the collection and use of information by LetGetMoreFollowers as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Please send any questions about LetGetMoreFollowers's Privacy Policy to: mailto:info@LETGETMOREFOLLOWERS.INFO

Please note that your use of the LetGetMoreFollowers network is governed by our terms and conditions.

(Revised March 10th, 2010)

© 2009 - 2010 Power By LetGetMoreFollowers. All rights reserved.  
LetGetMoreFollowers.info is Not Affiliated With OR Endorsed By Twitter.com.
